A Guide to the Laurance S. Rockefeller papers, Art Reference Files FA522
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Art Files, 2; 5.41 Cubic Feet 13 letter-size document boxes and 1 legal-size document box
  - Art Curators' Files, 1935-2006; 2
    - Jewelry - Invoices, Valuations, and Inventories, 1952-1971, 1997-1998 (Box 13, Folder 148)
      Purchases and insurance valuations; lists of LSR's and MFR's jewelry, consignments to Christie's, and family selections from MFR estate, 1997-1998.
    - Jewelry - Invoices, Valuations, and Inventories, 1952-1971, 1997-1998 (Box 13, Folder 148A)
    - Jewelry - Catalogue, 1954-1955 (Box 13, Folder 149)
      Inventory slips, lists, and memos from Carol Uht pertaining to the cataloguing of LSR's and MFR's jewelry collection (see the Art Reference Card Files in Series 1).
    - Jewelry - Insurance, 1955-1967 (Box 14, Folder 150)
      See also insurance schedules and valuations in the other jewelry files.
    - Jewelry - Insurance, 1955-1967 (Box 14, Folder 150A)
    - Photos of Mrs. Rockefeller's Jewelry (Box 14, Folder 151)
      Thirteen black and white photos (6.5" x 8.5" prints) by Raymond Yard. There are 37 individual jewelry pieces that are numbered on the prints, but there is no other identification of the jewelry or its owner.
    - LSR Estate - Ladies' Jewelry, 2004 July-August (Box 14, Folder 152)
    - LSR Estate - Ladies' Jewelry, 2004 July-August (Box 14, Folder 152A)
      Restricted -LSR Estate - Open in 2029
    - LSR Estate - Cuff Links and Stud Sets (2 folders), 2004 July-August (Box 14, Folder 153-154)
    - LSR Estate - Cuff Links and Stud Sets, 2004 July-August (Box 14, Folder 153A-154A)
    - LSR Estate - Gentlemen's Accessories (Volumes 1 and 2) (2 folders), 2004 July-August (Box 14, Folder 155-156)
    - LSR Estate - Gentlemen's Accessories (Volumes 1 and 2), 2004 July-August (Box 14, Folder 155A-156A)